Guide to the Rice University Office of Admissions records, 1979-2010 UA 142
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Office of Admissions records
1979-2010
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University
UA 142
20.5 Linear Feet (34 boxes)
Records reflecting the daily business of the Rice University Office of Admissions, including expense reports for faculty travel and for department spending, application records from potential faculty and graduate students, recruiting and documentation on incoming students.
Biographical / Historical
The Office of Admission handles new student admission and new faculty. It also promotes the university with travel and recruitment events.
Scope and Contents
Records reflecting the daily business of the Rice University Office of Admissions, including expense reports for faculty travel and for department spending, application records from potential faculty and graduate students, recruiting planning and documentation of incoming students.
Access Restrictions
This material is restricted for privacy reasons. Permission to use this material must be obtained in writing from the Director of Admissions.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred to the Woodson Research Center, 2007 and 2010.
Index Terms
Subjects
Universities and colleges
Document Types
reports
- Series I: 1985-2010, 110994
  - Admissions, Graduate, 1985, 110996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Boise Cascade, 2000, 110997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Boise Cascade 2001, 110998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Budget Transfers 1996-1997, 110999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - College Board/Educational Testing (Petersons), 111000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Check Request Forms 2005 (1 of 2), 111001 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Check Request Forms 2005 (2 of 2), 111002 (Box 1, Folder data_value_missing_7742d463a3902d002ac3cfa4f4862632)
  - Cingular 2003, 111003 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Comparison of Fund/Org. in SAS & SBS 2000-01, 111004 (Bin 2, Folder 1)
  - Counselor Fly-In 1998, 111005 (Bin 2, Folder 2)
  - CWS 1998, 111006 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - CWS 1999, 111007 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - CWS 2000, 111008 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Deposit Vouchers 1997, 111009 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Exeter 1 of 4 1999-2000, 111010 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Exeter 2 of 4 1999-2000, 111011 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Exeter 3 of 4 1999-2000, 111012 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Exeter 4 of 4 1999-2000, 111013 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1999 Exeter User Conference, 111014 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Expenses, July 1999, 111222 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Expenses, August 1999 (1 of 2), 111223 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Expenses, August 1999 (2 of 2), 111224 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Expenses, Sept. 1999 (1 of 2), 111225 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Expenses, Sept. 1999 (2 of 2), 111226 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Expenses, Oct. 1999 (1 of 2), 111227 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Expenses, Oct. 1999 (2 of 2), 111228 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Expenses, Nov. 1999, 111229 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Expenses, Dec. 1999, 111230 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Expenses, Jan. 2000, 111231 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Expenses, Feb. 2000, 111232 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Expenses, March 2000, 111233 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Expenses, April 2000, 111234 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Expenses, May 2000, 111235 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Expenses, June 2000 (1 of 3), 111236 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Expenses, June 2000 ( 2 of 3), 111237 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Expenses, June 2000 (3 of 3), 111238 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Facilities and Engineering, FY03, 111239 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Candidates, 1988-1989, 111240 (Box 5, Folder 4-14)
  - Faculty Candidates, 1987-1989, 111241 (Box 6, Folder 1-15)
  - Faculty Candidates, 1988-1989, 111266 (Box 7, Folder 1-3)
  - FA Balances 1988, 111269 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - G-H-I-J-K-L 1989, 111270 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Global Payments 2003, 111271 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - GRE's and Missing Items for Applications 1988-1989, 111272 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Applicants 1986-1987, 111273 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Graduate Applicants 1987-1988, 111274 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Applicant Stats 1988, 111275 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Candidate,1987-1988, 111276 (Box 7, Folder 11-12)
  - Graduate Tuition Worksheets- Continuing Studies Summer 2000, 111278 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - GRE Score Reports 1984-1989, 111279 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - GreenSheet 1988-1989, 111280 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - June-End Year Stationary Orders 1996, 111281 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - 70400 Mailroom/Postage FY1997 (1 of 2), 111282 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 70400 Mailroom/Postage FY1997 (2 of 2), 111283 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Math Tournament 1995, 111284 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Math Tournament 1996, 111285 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Math Tournament Feb. 21 1998, 111286 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Minority Fly-In 1994, 111287 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - National Merit Scholarship 1997, 111288 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - New Graduate Students 1999, 111289 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Owl Day Event April 15-17, 1994, 111290 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Owl Day 1995, 111291 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Owl Day 1996, 111292 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Owl Day 1997, 111293 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Owl Day 1998, 111294 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Owl Weekend 1999, 111295 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Owl Weekend 2000, 111296 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Owl Days 2010, 160596 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Pay Practices 1996, 111297 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - People on Leave of Absence 1997, 111298 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Personel Action Forms 1997, 111299 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Problems with Exeter 1999-2000, 111300 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Registration (1 of 3) 1999-2000, 111301 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Registration (2 of 3) 1999-2000, 111302 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Registration (3 of 3) 1999-2000, 111303 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - RU Postage & Delivery FY03, 111304 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - SAE 1996-2002, 111305 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Schwent Expenses 2003, 111306 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Student Aid 1998-2000 (1 of 3), 111307 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Student Aid 1998-2000 (2 of 3), 111308 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Student Aid 1998-2000 (3 of 3), 111309 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Student Requirements 2000, 111310 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Telecomm FY03 (1 of 2), 111311 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Telecomm FY03 (2 of 2), 111312 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Telecommunications FY05 (1 of 3), 111313 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Telecommunications FY05 (2 of 3), 111314 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Telecommunications FY05 (3 of 3), 111315 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Telecommunications Call Records Feb. 2005, 111316 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Tuition Eligibility 1999, 111317 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - UPS FY03, 111318 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - VillaFranca Expenses 2003, 111319 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Vision 1995, 111320 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Vision 1996, 111321 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Vision 1997 (1 of 2), 111322 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Vision 1997 (2 of 2), 111323 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Vision 1998, 111324 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Vision 1999 (1 of 2), 111325 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Vision 1999 (2 of 2), 111326 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Vision 2000, 111327 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Withdrawals 1997, 111328 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Series II: Staff Expense Reports, 2003-2004, 110995
  - Azzam, Eva Expense Reports 2003-2004, 111329 (Box 14, Folder 1-9)
  - Browning, Julie Expense Reports 2003-2004, 111331 (Box 14, Folder 10-25)
  - Connolly, Harriet Expense Reports, 2003-2004, 111332 (Box 14, Folder 26-37)
  - Heineman, Eric Expense Reports 2003-2004, 111330 (Box 15, Folder 1-20)
  - Jung, Suzanne Expense Reports 2004, 111333 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Lack, Cinda 2003-2004, 111334 (Box 15, Folder 22-28)
  - McAlister, Merritt Expense Reports 2003-2004, 111335 (Box 16, Folder 1-10)
  - McCaffety, Lisa Expense Reports 2003, 111336 (Box 16, Folder 11-12)
  - Pitre, Sarah Expense Reports 2003-2004, 111337 (Box 16, Folder 13-28)
  - Schwent/Shultz, Laura Expense Reports 2003-004, 111338 (Box 17, Folder 1-12)
  - Siler, Tamara Expense Reports 2003-2004, 111339 (Box 17, Folder 13-46)
  - Stein, Robert Expense Reports 2003, 111340 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Villafranca, Laura Expense Reports 2003-2004, 111341 (Box 17, Folder 48-66)
- Series III: Alphabetical Files, 1979-2004, 111342
  - Administrative Studies: Staffing Ratios, 1994, 111343 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Admissions Council: Statistical Reports, 1991-1997, 111344 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Admission Cycle: Yield Prediction 2001-2004, 111345 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Admissions Officers in Higher Education, by Terry Williams, 1985, 111346 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Wait List Admits Plan, 2002, 111347 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Workshops on Alumni in Admission, 1990-1991, 111348 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Concerns: Society of Latino Alumni, 1998, 111349 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Development: Summary of Enrollment/Resource Development Meeting, 2000, 111350 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Alumni: Rice Volunteeers for Admission (RAVA), 2001-2003, 111351 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Alumni: Roster of Alumni Secondary Teachers, 1998, 111352 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Application Data Trends, 1998-2002, 111353 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Application Evaluation: Blue Chip files, 1998-2001, 111354 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Application Evaluation: A Validity Study Predicting Freshman GPA, by Barry McFarland, 1996, 111355 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Application Evaluation: Financial Aid correspondence, 1998, 111356 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Application Evaluation: Language Requirement correspondence, 2000, 111357 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Application Evaluation: SAT II correspondence, 2000, 111358 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Application Processing: Admit Model presentation, 2000, 111359 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Application Processing: Electronic Application Agreement between Rice University and XAP Corporation, 2000, 111360 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Archives Committee correspondence, 1998, 111361 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Assistant Director Search, 2000, 111362 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Athletics: Grant-in-Aid Limitations, 1993, 111363 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Athletics: Policies for Admission of Student Athletes, 1996, 111364 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Barstow Parent Program, nd, 111365 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Bowdoin College Retreat workshop, 2000, 111366 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Brag Facts: University, 1999-2000, 111367 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Julie Mayberry Browning personal file, 1979-1981, 111368 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Case Studies: School Profiles, 2001, 111369 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Case Studies: Casady School, 1997, 111370 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Case Studies: Metairie Park School, 1995, 111371 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Case Studies: Pembroke Hill School, 1995, 111372 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Catalog Committee correspondence, 1994-1995, 111373 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - COHFE Retreat papers, 2000, 111374 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - College Board correspondence, 1980-1988, 111375 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - College Board meeting correspondence, 2000-2001, 111376 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - College Board EPS brochure, nd, 111377 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - College Urban Student contest entries, nd, 111378 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Commencement Programs, 1989 and 1994-2001, 111379 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Complaints/Compliments, 1995-2001, 111380 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Correpondence to enrolling student, 1998, 111381 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Counselor Fly-In seminar RSVPs, 1998, 111382 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Counselor Fly-In seminar expenses, 1998, 111383 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Counselor Fly-In seminar correspondence and photos, 1991, 111384 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Counselor Fly-In seminar attendees, 1998, 111385 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Counselor Fly-In seminar thank-you notes and evaluations, 1998, 111386 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Counselor Orientation/Duke University, 1988, 111387 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Enrollment: Attrition Statistics, 1997-1999, 111388 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Enrollment: Undergraduate Research Brochure, 2001, 111389 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Enrollment Planning: Student Information System Replacement Project, 1995-1997, 111390 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Enrollment Planning: Student Information System Progress Reports, 1997-1999, 111391 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Ethnic Statistics: Historical Data, 1989-2003, 111392 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Council correspondence, 2000, 111393 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Financial Aid: The 568 Group, 2001, 111394 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Financial Aid: Admission Deposit Statistics, 1995-1999, 111395 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Financial Aid: Finaid Training, 2000, 111396 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Financial Aid: Meeting Notes, Committee on Admissions and Student Financial Aid, 2000, 111397 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Financial Aid: Proposal for Merit Award program, 2000, 111398 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Financial Aid: Sample Letters to students, 2001, 111399 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Financial Aid: Software memo, 2001, 111400 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Fliers for Colleges, 1990, 111401 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Funding: Texas Higher Education Coordinating Board correspondence, 2001, 111402 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Hotel Contract between Rice and The Wyndham Warwick, 1998, 111403 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Hotel Expenses, 1993, 111404 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Interim Report on the Admissions Invterview at Rice, 1988, 111405 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Interviews: Roster of Senior Interviewers, 2001, 111406 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Iteneraries: Eric Heineman, 1998, 111407 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Itineraries: Tamara Siler, 1998-2001, 111408 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Management: Signature and Approval Authority for Contracts, 2001, 111409 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Media and Literature re: Admissions policies, 1985-1989, 111410 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Minority Recruitment Coordinator applicants, 1995, 111411 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous notes and memos (1 of 2), 111412 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous notes and memos (2 of 2), 111413 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - NACAC Conference materials, 1990, 111414 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - NACAC Conference materials, 1998, 111415 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - National Merit Scholarship High Scorers Roster, 1994, 111416 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Rice University Newcomer's Guide, 2000, 111417 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Rice University Newcomer's Guide, 1996, 111418 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Rice University Newcomer's Guide, 1997, 111419 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Rice University Newcomer's Guide, 1999, 111420 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Other Universities: Forms and Procedures for Smith College, 1999, 111421 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Outstanding Applicant Essays/Counselor's Recommendations, 1987, 111422 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Personnel: Performance Appraisal Forms, 1995, 111423 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Personnel: Sample Freshman Applications for Admission, 2002, 111424 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Personnel: Job Description Form, 1998, 111425 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Personnel: Policies, 1991-1999, 111426 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Personnel: Position Descriptions, 1987-1998, 111427 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Personnel: Prospective Admission Counselors, 1991-1996, 111428 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - President: Correspondence with Malcolm Gillis, 1994-1996, 111429 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - President: Inauguration Programs for Rupp and Gillis, 1985 & 1993, 111430 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Professional Development: Project Management Course, 1994, 111431 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Professional Organizations: COFHE (1 of 2), 111432 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Professional Organizations: COFHE (2 of 2), 111433 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Professional Organizations: COFHE Retreat Summer Meetings, 1998, 111434 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Professional Organizations: COFHE Comparative Information, 1995-1997, 111435 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Professional Organizations: ICUT correspondence, 2000, 111436 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Professional Organizations: Southern Consortium, 1994-1997, 111450 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Professional Organizations: Southern Consortium Seconds Conference, 1997, 111451 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Professional Organizations: Southern Consortium Dean's Retreat, 2001, 111453 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Professional Organizations: Standards for Success, 2001, 111455 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Publications: Correspondence, 1996-1997, 111456 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Registrar: Annual Reports, 2000-2003, 111457 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Registrar: Enrollment Reports to the President, 1997-1999, 111458 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Registrar: Enrollment Reports to the President, 1991-1996, 111459 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Registrar: Roster of Students recommended for Degrees, 1996, 111460 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Retreats: Owl Weekend, 2001, 111461 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Retreats: South Seas Resort, 1999-2000, 111462 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Rice Police Incident Report, 2002, 111463 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Rice Publications: Applications for Admission/Transfer (samples), 1991, 111464 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Rice Publications: CRA brochure, 1992, 111465 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Rice Publications: A Factual Sketch, 1992 and Factsheet 1995, 111466 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Rice Publications: Humanities at Rice (brochure), nd, 111467 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Rice Publications: Office of News and Publications correspondence, 1994-1995, 111468 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Rice Publications: Prospective CD for Hobson's, 1999, 111469 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Rice Publications: School of Engineering, 1989-1992, 111470 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Rice Publications: Shepherd School program leaflets, 1992, 111471 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Rice Publications: Boles Video notes, 2000, 111472 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Rice Publications: Recruitment video, 1997, 111473 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Rice Publications: proofs for Weiss school booklet, 1995, 111474 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Rice Recuitment Workshop, RSVPs, 1998, 111475 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - SACAC Conference materials, 1985-1987 (1 of 3), 111476 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - SACAC Conference materials, 1988-1991 (2 of 3), 111477 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - SACAC Self-Audit Development Guidelines, 1984, 111478 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - SACAC Conference materials, 1989 (3 of 3), 111479 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Scholarships: Bonham Fund, 1980-2000, 111480 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Scholarships: Coca-Cola, 1993, 111481 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Scholarships: Competitors for Awards, 1997-1999, 111482 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Scholarships: Haynie Scholar, 1975-2000, 111483 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Scholarships: HOBY Leadership Conference, 1993-1996, 111484 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Scholarships: Junior Achievement, 1999-2001, 111485 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Scholarships: Merit, 1991-1999, 111486 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Scholarships: National Achievement, 1995, 111487 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Scholarships: Other, 1992-1999, 111488 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Scholarships: Trauber, 2000, 111489 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Scholarships: Urban League of Houston, 1999-2000, 111490 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Scholarships: UT Health Science Center, 2001, 111491 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Scholarships: Westinghouse Science Talent Search, 1996, 111492 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Shepherd School of Music: Student Search, 2001, 111493 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Speeches and Workshops: Articles and Publications, 1992, 111494 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Speeches and Workshops: Burnout Workshop, 1996, 111495 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - St. John's School: Parent Workshop, 2002, 111496 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Staff Assistant Search: Resumes, 2001, 111497 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Statistics: Acceptance Rates, 2005, 111498 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Statistics: Acceptance Rates, 2000-2001, 111499 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Statistics: Acceptance Rates, 1999-2002, 111500 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Statistics: Admissions Summary, 1991-1999, 111501 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Statistics: Admission Data by State, 1995, 111502 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Statistics: Updates and Reports, 1991-1992, 111503 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Statistics: 1995-1996 Admission Cycle, 1996, 111504 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Statistics: 1994-1995 Admission Cycle, 1995, 111505 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Statistics: 1993-1994 Admission Cycle, 1994, 111506 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Statistics: 1992-1993 Admission Cycle, 1993, 111507 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Statistics: 1991-1992 Admission Cycle, 1992, 111508 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Statistics: COHFE definitions, 1998, 111509 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Statistics: Comparisons by Year, 1993-1996, 111510 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Statistics: Comparisons by Year, 1992-1993, 111511 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Statistics: Engineering Applicants, 1994, 111512 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Statistics: Decline Rates, 1999, 111513 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Statistics: Fact Sheet, 1997, 111514 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Statistics: 1997-1998 Admission Cycle, 1998, 111515 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Statistics: 1998-1999 Admission Cycle, 1999, 111516 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Statistics: 2000-2001 Admission Cycle, 2001, 111517 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Statistics: International Student Enrollment Report, 1996, 111518 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Statistics: Minority Students, 1990-1991, 111519 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Statistics: Predicting Yields, 1999-2000, 111520 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Statistics: Summaries, 1995-1998, 111521 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Statistics: Transfer Students, 1994-2001, 111522 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Statistics: Where They Went in 1998, 111523 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Statistics: 1999-2000 Admission Cycle, 2000, 111524 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Student Admission Council Concerns, 2000, 111525 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Student Affairs: Annual Reports to the Registrar, 1993, 111526 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Student Affairs: Career Services Center correspondence, 1993, 111527 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Student Affairs: Career Services Workshops, 1996, 111528 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Student Affairs: Clubs and Organizations, 1996, 111529 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Student Affairs: Health Coordinator Position, 1997, 111530 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Student Affairs: Phi Beta Kappa Inductees, 1993, 111531 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Student Affairs: Student Judicial Programs Annual Report, 1997, 111532 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Student Affairs: Student Orientation meeting notes, nd, 111533 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Surveys: Cambridge Associates, 2000, 111534 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Testing: College Entrance Examination Board materials, 1991-1993, 111535 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Testing: APIEL materials, 2000, 111536 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Testing: LOEP materials, 1994, 111537 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Testing: National Merit, 1999 (1 of 2), 111538 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Testing: National Merit, 1999 (2 of 2), 111539 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Testing: National Merit Scholarship Corporation Annual Report, 1999, 111540 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Testing: SAT materials, brochures, reports, 1990-95 (1 of 2), 111541 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Testing: SAT materials, brochures, reports, 1990-95 (2 of 2), 111542 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Testing: SAT materials, brochures, reports, 1996-2000, 111543 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Testing: TOEFL testing manual, brochures, reports, 1995-1997, 111544 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Travel: New England, 1992-1999, 111545 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Travel: EH Itineraries, 2001, 111546 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Travel: JMB Tennessee, 1991, 111547 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Travel: JMB New Hampshire and Massachusetts, 1994-1996, 111548 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Travel: JMB North Carolina, 2000, 111549 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Travel: Recruitment, 1992, 111550 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Travel: School Profiles, Brochures, etc., 1991-1995, 111551 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - University Offices: Health Professions Office Summary, 1996, 111552 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - University Offices: Equal Employment Opportunity and Affirmative Action, 2001, 111553 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - University Organizations: Rice Parking Committee Traffic and Parking Regulations booklet, 2001, 111554 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - University Organizations: Society of Families Leadership Committee, 1996, 111555 (Box 30, Folder 11)